MAHY MOHAB

UX/UI DESIGNER



CONTACT



Alexandria, Egypt



(+20) 0101884950



mahymohabm20@gmail.com



linkedin.com/mahvmohab209



behance.net/mahymohab

SKILLS

Tools

- · Figma, Figma Gem
- · Adobe XD
- · Photoshop, Gimp
- · Illustator CC
- VS Code

Technical Skills

- · Protoypes
- · Product Design
- · UI Minimalist design
- · Responsive web design
- · User Research
- Usability Testing
- Wireframing
- · HTML & HTML5
- Frameworks (Reactjs, Vuejs)
- NPM
- GitHub
- Shopify

PROFILE

Accomplished UI/UX Designer with 2+ experience Skilled in Figma, xd, photoshop, illustrator, specific in prototyping and minimalist UI design. Have completed several freelancing projects, including design of webapp, mobile apps, high fidelity wireframes, and improved UX for Technopolitan company and completed tasks 95% before the target.

EXPERIENCE

@ UI/UX DESIGNER | JUN 2021 - JAN 2022

FREELANCER

BOOKSY app

- · Created brand logo
- Designed 15+ app screens with high fidelity Wireframes

Recipe school app

 Created Interactive prototypes, Low to high fidelity Wireframes, Visual Design, and Logo.

Digita marketing website

landing page website with minimalist style and attractive scheme.

NFT marketplace website

- · landing page website with drak mode and light mode
- · ux study

Lotus moon app

- Created high fidelity Wireframes, 20+ screens with prototypes.
- · Created brand logo
- · UX case study

Redesign IKEA app case study

- · Created Interactive prototypes, Low fidelity
- · Wireframes, redesigned Visual Design, and
- loac
- · created UX case study with data flows and
- · personas.

MIDLEVEL UX/UI DESIGNER | JAN 2022 - PRESENT

TECHNOPOLITAN

- part of team include project managers and developers to create technically feasible design
- · creating 95% of CRM of the company
- creating user experience and interface using adobe XD for best user solution
- · finishing 80% of tasks before the target

LANGUAGE

Arabic mother toungue English fluent - B2 French Good - A2

EDUCATION

 COMPUTER AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, UNIVERSITY OF KAFR ELSHEIKH

B.S. in software engineering 2018 - 2022

- · Excellent in software engineering and agile methodology
- · very good all semesters with grade 3.1

CERTIFICATION

@ ADOBE XD CC 2020 | APR 2021

Udemy

UX DESIGN FUNDEMENTALS | NOV 2021 Mahara Tech

UI UX - FIGMA | FEB 2021 Udemy